Why did your father escape?
Mang Mario escaped?
Mikoy, did you know about this?
I'm not sure.
You know how much they love explosions.
Most of the time, literally.
Do you think she's back?
Huh?
Did I hear that right?
You met with Chiara.
When? Where?
I just didn't want you to worry anymore.
I worry every day.
Every single minute. You know that.
It looks like the Pinagpalas
are under police protection too.
Well,
at least then,
even if Chiara is far away from us,
she still has family with her.
It’s just…
La Morte Bianca is looking for them.
- Should we go to her?
- We can't.
The police still see us as the enemy.
As long as the Moravianos
are part of the Concordat,
all eyes will be on us.
This is exactly what I feared.
That one day we'd have to choose
between the Concordat and Chiara.
Stop it. He's just asking you.
You're useless!
Negative again.
Well, as expected,
Chiara got out of her handcuffs
within 24 hours.
But other than that,
she's very cooperative.
Are they giving you a hard time?
Come on, tell me.
The sooner we know,
the sooner we can solve it.
I don't think that even if I told you
the problem right away,
we'd be able to solve it that quickly.
Mr. Mario escaped.
What?
Mario escaped? When?
Last night, before Chiara arrived.
Where did he go?
We don't know, sir.
And sir, what complicates it even more,
is that when we asked Mikoy and Mrs. Tess,
they didn't know either.
He only left a letter.
A letter?
when one of you reports to the office,
bring that letter with you.
Okay, sir.
Sir, what is this?
Where is this? What happened?
Those are photos of the recent destruction
in a fishing community.
Barangay San Arsiso.
That's horrible.
They didn't even choose
their victims. Look, there are…
children and elderly people.
There are even people
with disabilities caught in it.
Chiara was right.
Isn't there anything we can do?
under Philippine law, no.
But here in the Philippines,
we can't even enforce
our local laws.
We can't just wait
for the next island
they're going to attack
and destroy.
so there are over 7,000 possibilities.
Really? Me?
Wait, did you…
run this by Agent Alex first?
We're dead.
It's not just
the information she has
about La Morte Bianca
and the Concordat
that she's offering us.
You're such a beautiful girl,
yet you're so stubborn.
It's just that…
Obviously,
I worked hard to earn
good standing in this safehouse.
And all of that could go to waste
because of what you're offering.
Sooner or later,
La Morte Bianca will find us.
There is a budget allocated to us
by the Presidential Office.
The problem is,
it's difficult to access.
So we have an additional budget,
but we can't access it?
What's going on?
Wait. Why me?
Why are you asking me?
One, you're not affiliated
with the Moravianos.
So you're not on La Morte Bianca's radar.
The agency isn't keeping
a close eye on you.
I'm just thinking,
if we end up teaming up with Chiara
and build a team around her,
wouldn't that be a bit
tricky and dangerous?
Because we won't just be
dealing with the Moravianos,
but the Concordat as well.
But haven't we
overcome our oppressors before?
The ones who colonized us.
That in this day and age,
we're the ones who need
to stand up for our country?
We will not be oppressed.
So you're really going through
with your plan?
Lastly,
I think you're the perfect fit
for this task
because I believe
I can count on you.
Sir, I don't want to rush this decision.
But because Chiara Valtrovi is involved,
I can't bring myself
to trust her just yet.
So my question is,
how exactly will we launch this plan?
Cocoy, what I'm asking you to do
isn't illegal.
It just doesn't have
the agency's permission.
But technically speaking,
you're still in the clear.
And most importantly,
the offer is substantial.
I didn't know you were nocturnal.
I'm just used to it.
My senses are sharper at night.
So tell me,
what's with this performative side of you?
I'm not being performative.
I'm adjusting too, just like you.
It seems like you're being
a little too nice and cooperative, Chiara.
You're being unfair to me, you know.
When I'm confident and assertive,
you think badly of me.
And now that I'm making an effort
and trying to be nice,
you still think badly of me.
So where do I stand with you, Alex?
I don't know, Chiara.
But between the two of us,
you're the one with a game plan.
Whatever it is,
stop it.
Try being genuine.
Because right now,
you're fake.
Like you're putting on a show.
Careful. You might get evicted.
Whatever you think about me,
you're wrong, Alex.
I hope so.
Because it'll be much worse if I'm right.
Even worse
if I never should've
trusted you in the first place.
You know, I get it.
Because honestly,
And I know you're protective
of everyone here.
But I don't think you're doing this
just because it's your job.
Wow.
Too bad it looks like
you're starting to convince my boss.
I don't know.
General Norberto thinks
your proposal is worth considering.
So he's going to accept my offer?
The protocols and policies
of your dear agency.
Don't worry.
I'll let you know
if you successfully convince my boss.
Are you not hiding any more secrets?
So dedicated, huh.
That'll make you stronger.
It'll toughen up your stomach.
- Good morning, Agent Alex.
- Morning, ma'am.
Now I know why Mikoy
is so in love with Chiara.
Because she's fearless.
She wasn't even intimidated
by the scary Agent Alex.
That's true.
As for me, I'm Team Alex.
Look at you acting like
you're so close to her.
On a different note.
Here's a thought. What if…
What if Mikoy had met Agent Alex first?
Do you think they'd still end up together?
Sure, they would.
They'd make a great pair.
Both handsome and beautiful.
- You guys, I swear.
- Hey, Mikoy!
No matter where you end up,
you still love gossiping
about other people's lives?
It's too early for that!
I bet you haven't even brushed
your teeth yet.
Come on, Mikoy.
On a different note,
I've got a serious question.
From what I know about you,
you're just a simple guy
who wants a simple life.
So why did you date
a mafia boss's daughter?
A boss, no less!
I don't know.
I guess that's what fate
had in store for me.
Come on. People make their own fate.
That's right. We may not have control
over everything,
but we always have a choice.
Look at you!
Is this what happens
when you stop drinking?
You're suddenly full of quotable quotes.
Of course, we're motivated.
After everything that's happened,
we've started asking ourselves
a lot of "what ifs".
Some pleasing scenarios.
You know.
Besides, buddy,
we're just concerned about you.
Thanks for your concern.
But instead of wasting our time
on "what ifs",
let's focus on what is.
"What if" isn't so bad either.
For today's activity,
I want you to draw and color
how you imagine Sitio San Juan
20 years from now.
Sounds good?
Mak-mak.
So, Sofie,
20 years from now, I'll be as tall as you,
so can I court you then?
Oh, Mak-mak!
Still no,
because 20 years from now,
I'll probably have a husband and kids.
What a shame!
Who do you want to be with in the future?
In the future?
Someone who's like my best friend,
someone I can tell anything to.
Even when we're married and have kids,
our friendship will still be the same.
So…
can we still be friends?
Of course!
If you still remember me.
Sounds like you don't want to.
Sofie, what about my future?
Oh, Mak-mak. You're still so young.
You know, your future
is still going to be bright.
Because you got to meet
the beautiful, smart,
and kind Sofie.
Right?
If it's a full house, you pay double!
What a delicious breakfast, sweetheart!
We have breakfast!
- Wow!
- Awesome!
Of course! Breakfast
is the most important meal of the day.
- Exactly.
- Wait a second.
It feels like something's missing.
You're right! Hot sauce.
And lots of calamansi.
And coffee creamer!
Okay, got it.
- Anything else?
- No, wait!
No, dear. That's not what I meant.
We're missing someone.
Cocoy isn't here!
- You're right!
- Yes.
Huh?
Cocoy is missing?
Where's Cocoy?
He's taking care of something.
Doing what?
Again, where is he, Chiara?
La Fornarina.
Looks like Cocoy left the country.
Dara, tell me that Sir Norberto
didn’t know about this yet.
Not yet.
Please, don’t let him know yet.
What is it that General
should not know and hear about?
Is there something I have to know?
What am I supposed to do?
Goodness, what’s happening?!